# Drew K Goodin

dkg@fastmail.com | (650) 307-5479 | SF Bay Area | https://drewgoodin.github.io

# **EDUCATION**

PURDUE UNIVERSITY | BS APPLIED MATHEMATICS

West Lafayette, IN | Aug 2005 - Jun 2010

| PART-TIME GRADUATE STUDY TO BEGIN 2023

## PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Multifaceted team player with a range of real world experiences from carpentry to database administration. Math-minded with an affinity for open-ended problems requiring creative solutions. An independent worker who you can trust to go and find the answer.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

#### SELF / BAY AREA BLIND, SHADE & SHUTTER | OWNER

Hayward, CA | Dec 2020 - Present

- · Built a profitable small business from the ground up
- Residential & commercial sales / installation of window fashions
- · All web development, server admin, marketing & SEO

#### VIGILENT INC. | TECHNICAL SUPPORT ENGINEER

Oakland, CA / Remote | Mar 2020 - Nov 2020

- First-line customer support for a highly technical AI-driven control systems software
- · Maintained and upgraded internal virtual machines for engineering testing
- · Performed on-site and virtual updates of customer systems
- Troubleshoot hardware and software malfunctions via log investigation & analysis

#### IND. CONTRACTOR | CARPENTER

Bay Areaa & Dallas, TX | Dec 2015 - Mar 2020

- · Professional sabbatical in order to learn a skilled trade.
- · Apprenticed with fine woodworkers and landscape carpenters, references available.
- Built & sold my own line of specialty cabinetry

#### PALO ALTO MEDICAL FOUNDATION | HRIS Specialist

Mountain View, CA | Mar 2012 - Apr 2014

- Wrote and maintained report queries on personnel data from HR information systems
- Processed employee data changes in accordance with company data & auditing standards
- Improved and owned a specialty project tracking nurse seniority with strict adherence to union agreements
- · Assisted compliance, payroll, and benefits departments for their data and reporting needs

# **SKILLS**

TECH Linux administration (Debian & RHEL), Perl programming, MySQL / MariaDB BUSINESS SOFTWARE Google Ads, WordPress & eCommerce, Salesforce, Advanced Excel incl. VBA

SOFT Exceptional customer service, follow-up, accountability

TRADE / CRAFT Finish carpentry, general handiwork, advanced AV setup and troubleshooting

### **ACADEMIC**

#### MATHEMATICAL INTERESTS

Functional analysis, computational algebra

#### REFERENCES AVAILABLE